vayable.com 2019-04-06

# Terms of Use | Vayable

Last Updated: August 19, 2013 

#### Welcome to Vayable!

Vayable, Inc. (“Vayable,” “we,” “us,” “our”) provides its services (described below) to you through its website located at www.vayable.com (the “Site”) and through its mobile applications and related services (collectively, such services, including any new features and applications, and the Site, the “Service(s)”), subject to the following Terms of Service (as amended from time to time, the “Terms of Service”). We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change or modify portions of these Terms of Service at any time. If we do this, we will post the changes on this page and will indicate at the top of this page the date these terms were last revised. We will also notify you, either through the Services user interface, in an email notification or through other reasonable means. Any such changes will become effective no earlier than fourteen (14) days after they are posted, except that changes addressing new functions of the Services or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. Your continued use of the Service after the date any such changes become effective constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms of Service. 

In addition, when using certain services, you will be subject to any additional terms applicable to such services that may be posted on the Service from time to time, including, without limitation, the Privacy Policy located at http://vayable.com/policy. All such terms are hereby incorporated by reference into these Terms of Service. 

#### Access and Use of the Service

##### Services Description:

The Service an online platform that connects locals who have unique knowledge of and experience with a particular travel destination or activity (“Providers”) with travelers seeking to receive services related to such destinations and activities (“Travelers”). Some Providers (“Guides”) lead experiences on the ground, and other Providers (“Insiders”) help with travel planning. Through the Services, Providers may create and post profiles (“Profiles”) that provide information about the Provider’s knowledge and experience, and may make themselves available to offer certain services to Travelers at a particular destination (each such service, an “Experience”). Travelers may select Providers (or may request that Vayable attempt to connect them to a Provider) to provide the Traveler with an Experience. 

##### Platform Nature of the Services:

Vayable makes available a platform for Travelers and Providers to meet online and arrange for Experiences. Vayable is not an operator of tours, activities or Experiences, nor is it a provider of tours or activities, and Vayable does not own, sell, resell, furnish, provide, manage and/or control any transportation or tour services. Vayable’s responsibilities are limited to: (i) facilitating the availability of the Services; (ii) serving as the limited agent of each Provider for the purpose of accepting payments from Travelers on behalf of the Provider; and (iii) in certain instances, booking lodging accommodations on behalf of Travelers as detailed below. 

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT VAYABLE IS NOT A PARTY TO ANY AGREEMENTS ENTERED INTO BETWEEN PROVIDERS AND TRAVELERS, NOR IS VAYABLE AN AGENT OR INSURER. THE SERVICES ARE INTENDED TO BE USED TO FACILITATE THE CONNECTIONS BETWEEN PROVIDERS AND TRAVELERS. VAYABLE CANNOT AND DOES NOT CONTROL THE CONTENT CONTAINED IN ANY PROFILES AND THE CONDITION, LEGALITY OR SUITABILITY OF ANY EXPERIENCES. VAYABLE HAS NO CONTROL OVER THE CONDUCT OF PROVIDERS, TRAVELERS AND OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICES OR ANY EXPERIENCES, AND DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY IN THIS REGARD. ACCORDINGLY, THE PLANNING OR PARTAKING OF ANY EXPERIENCESARE AT THE PROVIDER’S AND/OR TRAVELER’S OWN RISK. 

##### Your Registration Obligations:

You may be required to register with Vayable in order to access and use certain features of the Service. If you choose to register for the Service, you agree to provide and maintain true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the Service’s registration form. Registration data and certain other information about you are governed by our Privacy Policy. If you are under 13 years of age, you are not authorized to use the Service, with or without registering. In addition, if you are under 18 years old, you may use the Service, with or without registering, only with the approval of your parent or guardian. 

##### Member Account, Password and Security:

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, if any, and are fully responsible for any and all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to (a) immediately notify Vayable of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session when accessing the Service. Vayable will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Section. 

##### Modifications to Service:

Vayable reserves the right to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that Vayable will not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Service. 

##### General Practices Regarding Use and Storage:

You acknowledge that Vayable may establish general practices and limits concerning use of the Service, including without limitation the maximum period of time that data or other content will be retained by the Service and the maximum storage space that will be allotted on Vayable’s servers on your behalf. You agree that Vayable has no responsibility or liability for the deletion or failure to store any data or other content maintained or uploaded by the Service. You acknowledge that Vayable reserves the right to terminate accounts that are inactive for an extended period of time. You further acknowledge that Vayable reserves the right to change these general practices and limits at any time, in its sole discretion, with or without notice. 

##### Mobile Services:

The Service may includes certain services that are available via a mobile device, including (i) the ability to upload content to the Service via a mobile device, (ii) the ability to browse the Service and the Site from a mobile device and (iii) the ability to access certain features through an application downloaded and installed on a mobile device (collectively, the “Mobile Services”). To the extent you access the Service through a mobile device, your wireless service carrier’s standard charges, data rates and other fees may apply. In addition, downloading, installing, or using certain Mobile Services may be prohibited or restricted by your carrier, and not all Mobile Services may work with all carriers or devices. By using the Mobile Services, you agree that we may communicate with you regarding Vayable and other entities by SMS, MMS, text message or other electronic means to your mobile device and that certain information about your usage of the Mobile Services may be communicated to us. In the event you change or deactivate your mobile telephone number, you agree to promptly update your Vayable account information to ensure that your messages are not sent to the person that acquires your old number. 

##### Provider Obligations:

As a Provider, you may create Profiles that showcase your experience, activities you can lead, and the type of Experiences you can help Travelers plan. Profiles will be made publicly available via the Services, and other Members may contact you based upon the information provided in your Profile. You acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for your Profiles and your own acts and omissions and are also responsible for the acts and omissions of any individuals who are present during the Experience at your request or invitation, excluding the Traveler (and the individuals the Traveler invites to the Experience, if applicable). You agree to comply with the Vayable Provider Guidelines available at = link_to "www.community.vayable.com" 

You understand and agree that Vayable does not act as an insurer or as a contracting agent for you as a Provider. If a Traveler requests your expertise for a Experience and participates in your Experience, any agreement you enter into with such Traveler is between you and the Traveler and Vayable is not a party thereto. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Vayable serves as your limited authorized agent: 

  * for the purpose of accepting payments from Travelers on your behalf, and is responsible for transmitting such payments to you, subject to these Terms of Service, and
  * for the purpose of booking online lodging and accommodations (“Vayable Bookings”)
You are responsible for all other bookings, including without limitation on-the-ground arrangements, tours or experiences you host, restaurants and similar bookings. 

You represent and warrant that your Profile and your planning of and/or guidance on any Experience: 

  * will not breach any agreements you have entered into with any third parties (such as any agreements with or rules of employers or local tourism agencies)
  * will (a) be in compliance with all applicable laws, tax requirements, and rules and regulations that may apply to any such Experience, including, but not limited to, tourism, tour guide licensing laws, and other laws governing events and tours of public spaces and other venues and (b) not conflict with the rights of third parties.
Please note that Vayable assumes no responsibility for any Provider’s or Traveler’s compliance with any applicable laws, rules and regulations. Vayable reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to remove or disable access to any Profile for any reason, including Profiles that Vayable, in its sole discretion, considers to be objectionable for any reason, in violation of these Terms or otherwise harmful to the Services. 

Vayable recommends that Providers and Travelers obtain appropriate insurance for their Experiences. Please review any insurance policy that you may have for your Experience carefully, and in particular please make sure that you are familiar with and understand any exclusions to, and any deductibles that may apply for, such insurance policy, including, but not limited to, whether or not your insurance policy will cover the actions or inactions of Travelers (and the individuals the Traveler invites to the Experience, if applicable) while participating in your Experience. 

##### No Endorsement:

Vayable does not endorse any Experiences. In addition, although these Terms require users to provide accurate information, we do not attempt to confirm, and do not confirm, any user’s purported identity. You are responsible for determining the identity and suitability of others who you contact via the Services. We will not be responsible for any damage or harm resulting from your interactions with other users. By using the Services, you agree that any legal remedy or liability that you seek to obtain for actions or omissions of other users or other third parties will be limited to a claim against the particular user or other third parties who caused you harm and you agree not to attempt to impose liability on, or seek any legal remedy from Vayable with respect to such actions or omissions. Accordingly, we encourage you to communicate directly with other users via the Services regarding any bookings or Trips made by you. This limitation shall not apply to any claim by a Provider against Vayable regarding (i) the remittance of payments received from a Traveler by Vayable on behalf of a Provider or (ii) the failure of Vayable to book a Vayable Booking for which the Traveler provided accurate booking information, which instead shall be subject to the limitations described in the section below entitled “Limitation of Liability”. 

#### Conditions of Use

##### Bookings and Financial Terms for Providers:

1\. GUIDES (Providers who lead activities). Except in the case of a Pre-Approved Event (as defined below), if you are a Guide and a booking is requested for your Experience via the Services, you will be required to either confirm or reject the booking within the specified timeframe (which is generally within 24-48 hours of when the booking is requested, as determined by Vayable in its sole discretion) or the booking request will be automatically cancelled. If you are unable to confirm or decide to reject a booking of an Experience within the specified timeframe, any amounts collected by Vayable for the requested booking will be refunded to the applicable Traveler’s credit card and any pre-authorization of such credit card will be released. You may be able to create a Listing that is pre-scheduled for a specific time and date, where the Traveler’s booking may be automatically confirmed (a “Pre-Approved Event”). When a booking is requested via the Services, we may share with you the first and last name of the Traveler who has requested the booking and a link to the Traveler’s Vayable Account profile page. 

The fees displayed in each Listing are comprised of the Experience Fees (defined below) and the Traveler Fees (defined below). Where applicable, Taxes may be charged in addition to the Experience Fees and Traveler Fees. The Experience Fees, the Traveler Fees and applicable Taxes are collectively referred to in these Terms as the “Total Fees”. The amounts due and payable by a Traveler solely relating to a Guide’s Experience are the “Experience Fees”. Please note that it is the Guide and not Vayable which determines the Experience Fees. Vayable charges a fee to Travelers of three percent point nine (3.9%) of applicable Experience Fees which are the “Credit Card Fees”. The Traveler Fees are added to the Experience Fees to calculate the Total Fees (which will also include applicable Taxes) displayed in the applicable Listing. Vayable will collect the Total Fees at the time of booking confirmation (i.e. when the Guide confirms the booking within the specified timeframe) and will initiate payment of the Experience Fees (less Vayable’s Guide Fees (defined below)) to the Guide within 48 hours of when the Traveler arrives at the applicable Experience (except to the extent that a refund is due to the Traveler). However, please note that we will not be responsible for delays in remitting Experience Fees, which can vary based on the bank, payment provider, currency, location, etc. Be aware that in some instances it may take up to 30-60 days to receive funds as a result of bank and third-party payment provider process and regulations. 

2\. INSIDERS (Providers who plan travel). If you are a Provider and your assistance is requested by a Traveler via the Services, or Vayable desires to match you with a Traveler request, you will receive an email and text message containing information about the Traveler and his or her desired experiences, preferences and budget. You may review the provided information and should submit a proposal to the Traveler. After reviewing the proposal, the Traveler must pay a nonrefundable $45 fee to connect to Insider (“Connection Fee”). This fee is transferred to the Insider immediately after the Traveler books, less Vayable’s 25% commission (“Connection Commission”). After connection, this $45 will go toward any further services the Traveler Requests. 

Based on the amount of work you foresee investing in curating an itinerary for the travel Experience (“Itinerary”), you should negotiate an Insider service fee (“Service Fee”) with the Traveler. While setting the Service Fee is at your discretion, Vayable has some suggested pricing available at http://community.vayable.com/school. Vayable transfers the Service Fee to the Insider after final delivery of the Itinerary, less 25 percent commission (“Vayable Service Commission”). 

You may then continue to communicate with the Traveler until both parties have finalized an Itinerary. Once you and the Traveler have agreed on the Itinerary, you should send them the final proposed booking and price quoted for the Experience. 

Providers are also responsible for estimating the costs of all Experience expenses, for informing Vayable of the Vayable Bookings along with the applicable contact and booking information, and for booking all other Itinerary items. For Provider-booked Itinerary items, Providers will provide Vayable with a scanned copy of Provider’s government issued identification, and an itemized invoice of all expenses and any other information reasonably requested by Vayable. After the Traveler’s confirmed agreement to the Itinerary and Vayable’s receipt of payment from the Traveler, Vayable will remit to the Provider the total amount of Provider Commission and fees for the Provider-booked Itinerary items. 

In the event that actual prices for bookings have increased since the quoted price, Providers must contact the Traveler informing them of the price increase and requesting their permission to add the additional cost to the total fees charged to the Traveler. 

Each Provider hereby appoints Vayable as the Provider’s limited agent solely for the purpose of collecting payments made by Travelers on behalf of the Provider. Each Provider agrees that payment made by a Traveler to Vayable shall be considered the same as a payment made directly to the Provider and the Provider will make the Experience available to Traveler in the agreed upon manner as if the Provider has received the payment. In accepting appointment as the limited authorized agent of the Provider, Vayable assumes no liability for any acts or omissions of the Provider. 

Please note that Vayable does not currently charge fees for the creation of Profiles. However, you acknowledge and agree that Vayable reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to charge you for and collect fees from you for the creation of Profiles. Vayable will provide notice of any such fees via the Services prior to implementing such fees. 

Payment processing services for Insiders on Vayable are provided by Stripe and are subject to the [Stripe Connected Account Agreement](https://stripe.com/connect/account-terms) , which includes the [Stripe Terms of Service](https://stripe.com/terms) (collectively, the "Stripe Services Agreement"). By agreeing to these terms or continuing to operate as an Insider on Vayable, you agree to be bound by the Stripe Services Agreement, as the same may be modified by Stripe from time to time. As a condition of Vayable enabling payment processing services through Stripe, you agree to provide Vayable accurate and complete information about you and your business, and you authorize Vayable to share it and transaction information related to your use of the payment processing services provided by Stripe. 

##### Bookings and Fees for Travelers:

Travelers that wish to request the assistance of a Provider via the Services should provide the necessary information to Vayable regarding the Traveler’s desired experiences, preferences and budget. Vayable will endeavor to match the Traveler with a Provider with experience in the Traveler’s desired areas, and will connect the Traveler with a Provider in the event Vayable finds a match. Travelers may also directly contact Providers with a request. The Provider should propose an Experience itinerary after which the Traveler and the Provider should continue to communicate to finalize the itinerary. Once the itinerary is finalized, the Provider will either: 

  * confirm the Traveler’s reservation request for a guided experience or
  * send the Traveler the final proposed booking and price quote for curating the Experience (“Itinerary”), which the Traveler may confirm or reject.
Please note Vayable will charge a non-refundable service fee (“Vayable Service Fee”) on top of the price quote. 

For trips, Vayable is responsible for booking hotels and other lodging and accommodations that may be booked online (“Vayable Bookings”); the Provider is responsible for all other bookings (“Provider Bookings”). As part of the Booking, Travelers may be required to enter into an agreement (including releases) with the Provider, and the Traveler agrees to accept any terms, conditions, rules and restrictions associated with the Itinerary imposed by the Provider. Traveler acknowledges and agrees that Vayable is not a party to any agreement between the Traveler and Provider, and that, with the exception of its payment obligations and obligations related to Vayable Bookings hereunder, Vayable disclaims all liability arising from or related to any such agreements. Traveler acknowledges and agrees that, notwithstanding the fact that Vayable is not a party to any agreements between Traveler and the Provider, Vayable acts as the Provider’s payment agent for the limited purpose of accepting payments from Traveler on behalf of the Provider. Upon Traveler’s payment of amounts to Vayable which are due to the Provider, Traveler’s payment obligation to the Provider for such amounts is extinguished, and Vayable is responsible for remitting such amounts, less Vayable’s fees and commissions, to the Provider. In the event that Vayable does not remit any such amounts to a Provider, such Provider will have recourse only against Vayable. However, please note that we will not be responsible for delays in remitting payment, which can vary based on the bank, payment provider, currency, location, etc. Be aware that in some instances it may take up to 30-60 days to receive funds as a result of bank and third-party payment provider process and regulations and Vayable cannot be held liable for these delays. 

Please note that the actual amount charged by third parties for various items in the Itinerary may differ from the price quoted in the Booking, as prices may fluctuate before each booking is confirmed. If the actual prices are higher than the Total Fees, the Provider will contact you to request your permission prior to booking. 

#### Cancellations and Refunds:

**1\. GUIDES (Providers who lead activities).** These terms and conditions govern the Vayable Traveler Refund Policy (the “Traveler Refund Policy”) available to Travelers who book and pay for an Experience listed by a Guide through the Vayable platform (the “Site”) and suffer a Travel Issue and the obligations of the Guide associated with the Traveler Refund Policy. 

##### Travel Issue.

A “Travel Issue” means any one of the following: 

  * The Guide of the Experience (i) cancels a reservation within 24 hours before the scheduled start of the reservation, (ii) fails to arrive for the Experience within 20 minutes of the scheduled start time, or (iii) fails to provide the Traveler with the reasonable ability to access the Experience (e.g., by allowing the Traveler access to the space in which the Experience will happen or begin if applicable).
  * The description of the Experience in the listing on the Site is materially inaccurate with respect to (i) the duration of the Experience, (ii) the content of the Experience (including but not limited to the stated activities or sites, as applicable), or (iii) the physical location of the Experience. c) During the Traveler’s Experience, conditions do not meet safety or health hazards that would be reasonably expected, given the nature of the particular Experience, in Vayable’s judgment.

##### The Traveler Refund Policy.

If you are a Traveler and suffer a Travel Issue, we agree, at our discretion, to either (i) reimburse you up to the amount paid by you through the Site, as determined by Vayable in our discretion, depending on the nature of the Travel Issue suffered or (ii) use our reasonable efforts to find and book you another Experience which in our determination is reasonably comparable to the Experience described in your original reservation in terms of content and quality. For clarity, in the event the alternative Experience is of a higher price than the former, you may be responsible for any difference in price. In the event the alternative Experience is of a lower price, you may be entitled to a partial refund for the difference. All determinations of Vayable with respect to the Traveler Refund Policy, including without limitation the size of any refund, shall be final and binding on the Travelers and Guides. 

##### Conditions to Claim a Travel Issue.

Only a Traveler may submit a claim for a Travel Issue. If you are a Traveler, in order to submit a valid claim for a Travel Issue and receive the benefits with respect to your reservation, you are required to meet each of the following conditions: 

  * You must report the Travel Issue to Vayable in writing (at [support@vayable.com](mailto:support@vayable.com)) or via telephone and provide us with information (including evidence) about the Experience and the circumstances of the Travel Issue within 24 hours after the start of your reservation, and must respond to any requests by us for additional information or cooperation on the Travel Issue;
  * You must not have directly or indirectly caused the Travel Issue (through your action, omission or negligence); and
  * You must have used reasonable efforts to try to remedy the circumstances of the Travel Issue with the Guide prior to making a claim for a Travel Issue (and you must provide evidence of having done so).

##### Minimum Quality Standards, Guide Responsibilities and Reimbursement to Traveler.

If you are a Guide, you are responsible for ensuring that the Experiences you list on the Site meet minimum quality standards regarding adequacy of the description on the Site, safety, health, and do not present a Traveler with Travel Issues. Throughout the Experience, Guides should be available in order to try, in good faith, to resolve Traveler issues. 

If you are a Guide, and if (i) Vayable determines that a Traveler has suffered a Travel Issue related to an Experience listed by you and (ii) Vayable either reimburses that Traveler any amount up to the amount paid by the Traveler through the Site for the Experience or provides an alternative Experience to the Traveler, you agree to reimburse Vayable up to the amount paid by Vayable within 30 days of Vayable’s request. All determinations of Vayable with respect to the Traveler Refund Policy, including without limitation the size of any refund to the Traveler, shall be final and binding on the Travelers and Guides. You also agree that in order for you to reimburse Vayable up to the amount paid by Vayable, Vayable may off-set or reduce any amounts owed by Vayable to you by this amount. If the Traveler is rescheduled to an alternative Experience, you may lose part or all of the Experience Fee payment for the booking and you may be responsible for reasonable additional costs incurred to reschedule the Traveler to the alternative Experience. 

The rights of the Travelers under the Traveler Refund Policy supersede the cancellation policy that otherwise applies to a particular Experience. If you dispute the Travel Issue you may notify us in writing ([support@vayable.com](mailto:support@vayable.com)) or via telephone and provide us with information (including evidence) disputing the claims regarding the Travel Issue, provided you must have used reasonable and good faith efforts to try to remedy the Travel Issue with the Traveler prior to disputing the Travel Issue claim (and you must provide evidence of having done so). You agree that all determinations of Vayable with respect to the Travel Issue shall be final and binding on the Travelers and Guides regardless of your submission of a dispute against such Travel Issue. In the event of one or more 

Travel Issues, Vayable, in its discretion, may elect to take additional actions. These actions include, but are not limited to, negatively affecting your listing ranking, automated reviews or notifications indicating Travel Issues, canceling future bookings, suspending or removing the listing of the Experience or imposing penalties or fees for the administrative burden associated with the Travel Issues. 

##### General Provisions.

(a) No Assignment/No Insurance. This Traveler Refund Policy is not intended to constitute an offer to insure, does not constitute insurance or an insurance contract, does not take the place of insurance obtained or obtainable by the Traveler, and the Traveler has not paid any premium in respect of the Traveler Refund Policy. The benefits provided under this Traveler Refund Policy are not assignable or transferable by you. (b) Modification or Termination. Vayable reserves the right to modify or terminate this Traveler Refund Policy, at any time, in its sole discretion, and without prior notice. (c) If Vayable modifies this Traveler Refund Policy, we will post the modification on the Site or provide you with notice of the modification and Vayable will continue to process all claims for Travel Issues made prior to the effective date of the modification. (d) Entire Agreement and Definitions. This Traveler Refund Policy constitutes the entire and exclusive understanding and agreement between Vayable and you regarding the Traveler Refund Policy and supersedes and replaces any and all prior oral or written understandings or agreements between Vayable and you regarding the Traveler Refund Policy. Capitalized terms not otherwise defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in the Vayable Terms of Service. Controlling Law. This Traveler Refund Policy will be interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of California and the United States of America, without regard to its conflict-of-law provisions. (e) Limitation of Liability. IN NO EVENT WILL VAYABLE’S AGGREGATE LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS VAYABLE POLICY TERMS, EXCEED THE AMOUNT OF THE EXPERIENCE FEES COLLECTED BY VAYABLE FROM THE TRAVELER. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, BY POSTING A LISTING OR BOOKING AN EXPERIENCE OR OTHERWISE USING THE SITE, SERVICES AS A GUIDE OR TRAVELER, YOU ARE INDICATING THAT YOU HAVE READ, AND THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE POLICY TERMS. 

**2\. INSIDERS (Providers who plan travel).** Travelers are free to reject any Itinerary for any reason prior to payment. Once an Itinerary is confirmed by a Traveler, any fees paid are non-refundable except as set forth below: 

##### Traveler cancels.

Vayable will endeavor to refund Traveler the fees paid for any Itinerary items that have not yet been booked, minus the Service Fee. Fees for Itinerary items that have already been booked are non-refundable. 

##### Provider cancels.

Whenever possible Vayable will connect Traveler to an alternate Provider who can fulfill request. If not, Vayable will refund the Total Fees for such booking to the applicable Traveler within a commercially reasonable time of the cancellation. 

##### Cancellation due to outside factors.

Certain Experiences may depend on factors outside either party’s control, such as weather (“Outside Factors”). The Provider has the discretion as to whether Outside Factors will prevent the Experience from taking place. As a Provider, if you need to cancel an Experience due to Outside Factors, you must contact the Traveler and Vayable (at [support@vayable.com](mailto:support@vayable.com)) as early as possible. Subject to the Traveler’s consent, the Provider and the Traveler may choose to reschedule the Experience for another date. If the Experience cannot be rescheduled, the Traveler should contact Vayable so we may assist in finding a replacement Experience. For clarity, in the event the alternative Experience is of a higher price than the former, you may be responsible for any difference in price. In the event the alternative Experience is of a lower price, you may be entitled to a partial refund for the difference. As a Traveler, if you have contacted Vayable as provided above and Vayable is unable to find you a replacement Experience, Vayable may refund the Total Fees for such booking to the applicable Traveler within a commercially reasonable time of the cancellation. 

#### Taxes:

You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for determining your applicable tax reporting requirements in consultation with your tax advisors. Vayable cannot and does not offer tax-related advice to any users of the Services. Additionally, please note that each Provider is responsible for determining local indirect taxes and for including any applicable taxes to be collected or obligations relating to applicable taxes within Itineraries. 

#### User Conduct:

You are solely responsible for all code, video, images, information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, messages or other materials (“content”) that you upload, post, publish or display (hereinafter, “upload”) or email or otherwise use via the Service. The following are examples of the kind of content and/or use that is illegal or prohibited by Vayable. Vayable reserves the right to investigate and take appropriate legal action against anyone who, in Vayable’s sole discretion, violates this provision, including without limitation, removing the offending content from the Service, suspending or terminating the account of such violators and reporting you to the law enforcement authorities. You agree to not use the Service to: 

  * Email or otherwise upload any content that (i) infringes any intellectual property or other proprietary rights of any party; (ii) you do not have a right to upload under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships; (iii) contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment; (iv) poses or creates a privacy or security risk to any person; (v) constitutes unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, commercial activities and/or sales, “junk mail,” “spam,” “chain letters,” “pyramid schemes,” “contests,” “sweepstakes,” or any other form of solicitation; (vi) is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortious, excessively violent, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, pornographic, libelous, invasive of another’s privacy, hateful racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable; or (vii) in the sole judgment of Vayable, is objectionable or which restricts or inhibits any other person from using or enjoying the Service, or which may expose Vayable or its users to any harm or liability of any type;
  * Interfere with or disrupt the Service or servers or networks connected to the Service, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the Service; or
  * Violate any applicable local, state, national or international law, or any regulations having the force of law;
  * Impersonate any person or entity, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;
  * Solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18;
  * Harvest or collect email addresses or other contact information of other users from the Service by electronic or other means for the purposes of sending unsolicited emails or other unsolicited communications;
  * Advertise or offer to sell or buy any goods or services for any business purpose that is not specifically authorized;
  * Further or promote any criminal activity or enterprise or provide instructional information about illegal activities; or
  * Obtain or attempt to access or otherwise obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the Service;
  * Offer, as a Provider, any Experiences that you do not yourself have permission to provide (without limiting the foregoing, you will not list Experiences as a Provider if you are serving in the capacity of an agent for a third party);
  * Offer, as a provider, any Experience that may not be provided pursuant to the terms and conditions of an agreement with a third party;
  * Contact a Provider for any purpose other than asking a question related to a booking, such Provider’s Experiences or Profiles;
  * Contact a Traveler for any purpose other than asking a question related to a booking or such Traveler’s use of the Services;
  * When acting as a Traveler or otherwise, recruit or otherwise solicit any Provider or other user of the Services to join third party services or websites that are competitive to Vayable, without Vayable’s prior written approval;
  * Use the Services to find a Provider or Traveler and then complete a booking of an Experience transaction independent of the Services, whether or not you do so in order to circumvent the obligation to pay any Service Fees related to Vayable’s provision of the Services; or
  * As a Provider, submit any Profile or Itinerary with a false or misleading price information.

##### Special Notice for International Use; Export Controls:

Software (defined below) available in connection with the Service and the transmission of applicable data, if any, is subject to United States export controls. No Software may be downloaded from the Service or otherwise exported or re-exported in violation of U.S. export laws. Downloading or using the Software is at your sole risk. Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all local rules and laws regarding your use of the Service, including as it concerns online conduct and acceptable content. 

##### Commercial Use:

Unless otherwise expressly authorized herein or in the Service, you agree not to display, distribute, license, perform, publish, reproduce, duplicate, copy, create derivative works from, modify, sell, resell, exploit, transfer or upload for any commercial purposes, any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service. The Service is for your personal use. 

##### Apple-Enabled Software Applications:

Vayable offers Software applications that are intended to be operated in connection with products made commercially available by Apple Inc. (“Apple”), among other platforms. With respect to Software that is made available for your use in connection with an Apple-branded product (such Software, “Apple-Enabled Software”), in addition to the other terms and conditions set forth in these Terms of Service, the following terms and conditions apply: 

  * Vayable and you acknowledge that these Terms of Service are concluded between Vayable and you only, and not with Apple, and that as between Vayable and Apple, Vayable, not Apple, is solely responsible for the Apple-Enabled Software and the content thereof.
  * You may not use the Apple-Enabled Software in any manner that is in violation of or inconsistent with the Usage Rules set forth for Apple-Enabled Software in, or otherwise be in conflict with, the App Store Terms of Service.
  * Your license to use the Apple-Enabled Software is limited to a non-transferable license to use the Apple-Enabled Software on an iOS Product that you own or control, as permitted by the Usage Rules set forth in the App Store Terms of Service.
  * Apple has no obligation whatsoever to provide any maintenance or support services with respect to the Apple-Enabled Software.
  * Apple is not responsible for any product warranties, whether express or implied by law. In the event of any failure of the Apple-Enabled Software to conform to any applicable warranty, you may notify Apple, and Apple will refund the purchase price for the Apple-Enabled Software to you, if any; and, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Apple will have no other warranty obligation whatsoever with respect to the Apple-Enabled Software, or any other claims, losses, liabilities, damages, costs or expenses attributable to any failure to conform to any warranty, which will be Vayable’s sole responsibility, to the extent it cannot be disclaimed under applicable law.
  * Vayable and you acknowledge that Vayable, not Apple, is responsible for addressing any claims of you or any third party relating to the Apple-Enabled Software or your possession and/or use of that Apple-Enabled Software, including, but not limited to: (i) product liability claims; (ii) any claim that the Apple-Enabled Software fails to conform to any applicable legal or regulatory requirement; and (iii) claims arising under consumer protection or similar legislation.
  * In the event of any third party claim that the Apple-Enabled Software or the end-user’s possession and use of that Apple-Enabled Software infringes that third party’s intellectual property rights, as between Vayable and Apple, Vayable, not Apple, will be solely responsible for the investigation, defense, settlement and discharge of any such intellectual property infringement claim.
  * You represent and warrant that (i) you are not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo, or that has been designated by the U.S. Government as a “terrorist supporting” country; and (ii) you are not listed on any U.S. Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.
  * If you have any questions, complaints or claims with respect to the Apple-Enabled Software, they should be directed to Vayable as follows: [support@vayable.com](mailto:support@vayable.com) or 1-855-GO-VAYABLE

Vayable and you acknowledge and agree that Apple, and Apple’s subsidiaries, are third party beneficiaries of these Terms of Service with respect to the Apple-Enabled Software, and that, upon your acceptance of the terms and conditions of these Terms of Service, Apple will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce these Terms of Service against you with respect to the Apple-Enabled Software as a third party beneficiary thereof. 

#### Intellectual Property Rights

##### Service Content, Software and Trademarks:

You acknowledge and agree that the Service may contain content or features (“Service Content”) that are protected by copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights and laws. Except as expressly authorized by Vayable, you agree not to modify, copy, frame, scrape, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute or create derivative works based on the Service or the Service Content, in whole or in part, except that the foregoing does not apply to your own User Content (as defined below) that you legally upload to the Service. In connection with your use of the Service you will not engage in or use any data mining, robots, scraping or similar data gathering or extraction methods. Any use of the Service or the Service Content other than as specifically authorized herein is strictly prohibited. The technology and software underlying the Service or distributed in connection therewith is the property of Vayable, our affiliates and our partners (the “Software”). You agree not to copy, modify, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, reverse assemble or otherwise attempt to discover any source code, sell, assign, sublicense, or otherwise transfer any right in the Software. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by Vayable. 

The Vayable name and logos are trademarks and service marks of Vayable (collectively the “Vayable Trademarks”). Other Vayable, product, and service names and logos used and displayed via the Service may be trademarks or service marks of their respective owners who may or may not endorse or be affiliated with or connected to Vayable. Nothing in this Terms of Service or the Service should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any of Vayable Trademarks displayed on the Service, without our prior written permission in each instance. All goodwill generated from the use of Vayable Trademarks will inure to our exclusive benefit. 

##### Third Party Material:

Under no circumstances will Vayable be liable in any way for any content or materials of any third parties (including users), including, but not limited to, for any errors or omissions in any content, or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any such content. You acknowledge that Vayable does not have a duty to pre-screen content, but that Vayable and its designees will have the right (but not the obligation) in their sole discretion to refuse or remove any content that is available via the Service. Without limiting the foregoing, Vayable and its designees will have the right to remove any content that violates these Terms of Service or is deemed by Vayable, in its sole discretion, to be otherwise objectionable. You agree that you must evaluate, and bear all risks associated with, the use of any content, including any reliance on the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of such content. 

##### User Content Transmitted Through the Service:

With respect to the content or other materials you upload through the Service or share with other users or recipients (collectively, “User Content”), you represent and warrant that you own all right, title and interest in and to such User Content, including, without limitation, all copyright and rights of publicity contained therein. By uploading any User Content you hereby grant and will grant Vayable and its affiliated companies a nonexclusive, worldwide, royalty free, fully paid up, transferable, sublicensable, perpetual, irrevocable license to copy, display, upload, perform, distribute, store, modify and otherwise use your User Content in connection with the operation of the Service or the promotion, advertising or marketing thereof, in any form, medium or technology now known or later developed. 

You acknowledge and agree that any questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, feedback or other information about the Service (“Submissions”), provided by you to Vayable are non-confidential and Vayable will be entitled to the unrestricted use and dissemination of these Submissions for any purpose, commercial or otherwise, without acknowledgment or compensation to you. 

You acknowledge and agree that Vayable may preserve content and may also disclose content if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process, applicable laws or government requests; (b) enforce these Terms of Service; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Vayable, its users and the public. You understand that the technical processing and transmission of the Service, including your content, may involve (a) transmissions over various networks; and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. 

##### Third Party Websites:

The Service may provide, or third parties may provide, links or other access to other sites and resources on the Internet. Vayable has no control over such sites and resources and Vayable is not responsible for and does not endorse such sites and resources. You further acknowledge and agree that Vayable will not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any content, events, goods or services available on or through any such site or resource. Any dealings you have with third parties found while using the Service are between you and the third party, and you agree that Vayable is not liable for any loss or claim that you may have against any such third party. 

##### Social Networking Services:

You may enable or log in to the Service via various online third party services, such as social media and social networking services like Facebook or Twitter (“Social Networking Services”). By logging in or directly integrating these Social Networking Services into the Service, we make your online experiences richer and more personalized. To take advantage of this feature and capabilities, we may ask you to authenticate, register for or log into Social Networking Services on the websites of their respective providers. As part of such integration, the Social Networking Services will provide us with access to certain information that you have provided to such Social Networking Services, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. For more information about the implications of activating these Social Networking Services and Vayable’s use, storage and disclosure of information related to you and your use of such services within Vayable (including your friend lists and the like), please see our Privacy Policy. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Networking Services use, store and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and Vayable shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any third party site or service that may be enabled within the Service. 

In addition, Vayable is not responsible for the accuracy, availability or reliability of any information, content, goods, data, opinions, advice or statements made available in connection with Social Networking Services. As such, Vayable is not liable for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such Social Networking Services. Vayable enables these features merely as a convenience and the integration or inclusion of such features does not imply an endorsement or recommendation. 

##### Indemnity and Release:

You agree to release, indemnify and hold Vayable and its affiliates and their officers, employees, directors and agent harmless from any from any and all losses, damages, expenses, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, rights, claims, actions of any kind and injury (including death) arising out of or relating to your use of the Service, any User Content, your connection to the Service, your violation of these Terms of Service or your violation of any rights of another. If you are a California resident, you waive California Civil Code Section 1542, which says: “A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor.” If you are a resident of another jurisdiction, you waive any comparable statute or doctrine. 

##### Disclaimer of Warranties:

YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. VAYABLE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. 

VAYABLE MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT (I) THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (II) THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE, (III) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SERVICE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, OR (IV) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS. 

##### Limitation of Liability:

YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT VAYABLE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF VAYABLE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, RESULTING FROM: (I) THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICE; (II) THE COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS AND SERVICES RESULTING FROM ANY GOODS, DATA, INFORMATION OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED OR MESSAGES RECEIVED OR TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICE; (III) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA; (IV) STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON THE SERVICE; OR (V) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE SERVICE. IN NO EVENT WILL VAYABLE’S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES OR CAUSES OF ACTION EXCEED THE AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID VAYABLE IN THE LAST SIX (6) MONTHS, OR, IF GREATER, ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS ($100). 

SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS SET FORTH ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE SERVICE OR WITH THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USE OF THE SERVICE. 

##### Arbitration:

At Vayable’s or your election, all disputes, claims, or controversies arising out of or relating to the Terms of Service or the Service that are not resolved by mutual agreement may be resolved by binding arbitration to be conducted before JAMS, or its successor. Unless otherwise agreed by the parties, arbitration will be held in San Francisco, California before a single arbitrator mutually agreed upon by the parties, or if the parties cannot mutually agree, a single arbitrator appointed by JAMS, and will be conducted in accordance with the rules and regulations promulgated by JAMS unless specifically modified in the Terms of Service. The arbitration must commence within forty-five (45) days of the date on which a written demand for arbitration is filed by either party. The arbitrator’s decision and award will be made and delivered within sixty (60) days of the conclusion of the arbitration and within six (6) months of the selection of the arbitrator. The arbitrator will not have the power to award damages in excess of the limitation on actual compensatory, direct damages set forth in the Terms of Service and may not multiply actual damages or award punitive damages or any other damages that are specifically excluded under the Terms of Service, and each party hereby irrevocably waives any claim to such damages. The arbitrator may, in his or her discretion, assess costs and expenses (including the reasonable legal fees and expenses of the prevailing part) against any party to a proceeding. Any party refusing to comply with an order of the arbitrators will be liable for costs and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, incurred by the other party in enforcing the award. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the case of temporary or preliminary injunctive relief, any party may proceed in court without prior arbitration for the purpose of avoiding immediate and irreparable harm. The provisions of this arbitration section will be enforceable in any court of competent jurisdiction. 

##### Termination:

You agree that Vayable, in its sole discretion, may suspend or terminate your account (or any part thereof) or use of the Service and remove and discard any content within the Service, for any reason, including, without limitation, for lack of use or if Vayable believes that you have violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit of these Terms of Service. Any suspected fraudulent, abusive or illegal activity that may be grounds for termination of your use of Service, may be referred to appropriate law enforcement authorities. Vayable may also in its sole discretion and at any time discontinue providing the Service, or any part thereof, with or without notice. You agree that any termination of your access to the Service under any provision of this Terms of Service may be effected without prior notice, and acknowledge and agree that Vayable may immediately deactivate or delete your account and all related information and files in your account and/or bar any further access to such files or the Service. Further, you agree that Vayable will not be liable to you or any third party for any termination of your access to the Service. 

##### User Disputes:

You agree that you are solely responsible for your interactions with any other user in connection with the Service and Vayable will have no liability or responsibility with respect thereto. Vayable reserves the right, but has no obligation, to become involved in any way with disputes between you and any other user of the Service. 

##### General:

These Terms of Service constitute the entire agreement between you and Vayable and govern your use of the Service, superseding any prior agreements between you and Vayable with respect to the Service. You also may be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you use affiliate or third-party services, third-party content or third-party software. These Terms of Service will be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions. With respect to any disputes or claims not subject to arbitration, as set forth above, you and Vayable agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts located within San Francisco County, California. The failure of Vayable to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Service will not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of these Terms of Service is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties’ intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of these Terms of Service remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of the Service or these Terms of Service must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form will be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. You may not assign this Terms of Service without the prior written consent of Vayable, but Vayable may assign or transfer this Terms of Service, in whole or in part, without restriction. The section titles in these Terms of Service are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect. Notices to you may be made via either email or regular mail. The Service may also provide notices to you of changes to these Terms of Service or other matters by displaying notices or links to notices generally on the Service. 

##### Your Privacy:

At Vayable, we respect the privacy of our users. For details please see our Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you consent to our collection and use of personal data as outlined therein. 

##### Notice for California Users:

Under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, users of the Service from California are entitled to the following specific consumer rights notice: The Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs may be contacted in writing at 1625 North Market Blvd., Suite N 112, Sacramento, CA 95834, or by telephone at (916) 445-1254 or (800) 952-5210. You may contact us at Vayable, Inc., 1-855-GO-VAYABLE. 

##### Questions? Concerns? Suggestions?

Please contact us at [support@vayable.com](mailto:support@vayable.com) to report any violations of these Terms of Service or to pose any questions regarding this Terms of Service or the Service. 

Last Updated: May 23, 2018 

Vayable, Inc. (“Vayable”, “we” or “us”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Data we receive from users of www.vayable.com (the “Site”) and any related applications (the “Application”) and otherwise, through the Service. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your Vayable Account) or by means of a notice via the Service prior to the change becoming effective. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service (at www.vayable.com). 

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally. 

International Transfer 

YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO - AND MAINTAINED ON - COMPUTERS LOCATED OUTSIDE OF YOUR STATE, PROVINCE, COUNTRY OR OTHER GOVERNMENTAL JURISDICTION WHERE THE PRIVACY LAWS MAY NOT BE AS PROTECTIVE AS THOSE IN YOUR JURISDICTION. IF YOU ARE LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES AND CHOOSE TO PROVIDE INFORMATION TO US, VAYABLE TRANSFERS PERSONAL DATA TO THE UNITED STATES AND PROCESSES IT THERE. YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOLLOWED BY YOUR SUBMISSION OF SUCH INFORMATION REPRESENTS YOUR AGREEMENT TO THAT TRANSFER. 

Information Collection and Use 

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, Application, services, features and content (collectively, the “Service”), to administer your use of the Service and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Service. 

Personally Identifiable Information 

When you register with us through the Service and become a Member and when you choose to post a Listing or book an Experience, or when you wish to contact another Member, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Identity Information”). Identity Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, email address, social security number (SSN), government-issued identification card, and home postal address, but does not include your credit card number or billing information. In order to process some of your transactions through the Service, we may also ask for your credit card number and other billing information (“Billing Information”). We may collect information about your precise or approximate location as determined through data such as your IP address or mobile device’s GPS to offer you an improved user experience. Most mobile devices allow you to control or disable the use of location services for applications in the device’s settings menu. Vayable may also collect this information even when you are not using the app if this connection is enabled through your settings or device permissions. (Identity Information, Billing Information and geolocation information together, “Personal Data”). If the address associated with a Listing you post matches that of your credit card billing address, that address would be considered Identity Information. Some Personal Data may be required, like your name and email address, and other Personal Data may be optional, like your date of birth. We use your Personal Data to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. 

We collect Personal Data in connection with your registration to join the Service. You can register to join via the Service by completing the required forms. 

You may also be permitted to register by logging into online accounts you may have with third party service providers (“SNS”) (e.g. Facebook); each such account, a “Third Party Account”, via the Service as described below. As part of the functionality of the Service, you may link your Vayable Account with Third Party Accounts, by either: (i) providing your Third Party Account login information to Vayable through the Service; or (ii) allowing Vayable to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to Vayable and/or grant Vayable access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for use for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating Vayable to pay any fees or making Vayable subject to any usage limitations imposed by the applicable SNS. If you decide to register by logging into a Third Party Account via the Service, we will obtain the Personal Data you have provided to the applicable SNS (such as your name, email address, profile picture, names of SNS friends, names of SNS groups to which you belong, other information you make publicly available via the applicable SNS and/or other information you authorize Vayable to access by authorizing the SNS to provide such information) from your Third Party Accounts and use that information to create your Vayable Account and Vayable Account profile page and you will become a Member. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, you understand that by granting us access to the Third Party Accounts, we will access, make available and store (if applicable and as permitted by the SNS and authorized by you) the information in your Third Party Accounts so that it is available on and through your Vayable Account on the Service. If there is information about your “friends” your Third Party Account, the information we obtain about those friends, may also depend on the privacy settings such people have with the applicable SNS. 

We may also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your Vayable Account profile (e.g., without limitation, zip code (on its own) and individual preferences or demographic information) (“Non-Identifying Information”). 

We use your Personal Data (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries. 

Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Data if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your demographic information). We may combine your Personal Data with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Vayable Users (defined below) to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how the Service is used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions. 

We also use your Personal Data to contact you with Vayable newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or contact us as detailed in the “Changing or Deleting Information” section, below. Please note that we may also use your Personal Data to contact you with information related to your use of the Service; you may not opt out of these notifications. 

Log Data 

When you visit the Service, whether as a Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “Vayable User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Service, pages of the Service that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on the Service, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Service and for the Service’s technical administration, to increase the Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor the Service to our visitors' and users’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to and users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Data or use it in association with other Personal Data, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information. 

Cookies 

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Service and help us analyze Service usage more accurately. For instance, our Service may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Service without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Service. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. Third party advertisers on the Service may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. We may also use Flash cookies, which operate differently than browser cookies and cookie management tools available in a web browser may not remove flash cookies. To learn more about and manage flash cookies you can visit adobe.com and make changes at the privacy settings panel. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Service or all functionality of the Service. 

Web Beacons 

Our Site and Application may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs), which would be used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how the Service is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This would allow us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns. 

Sending Messages Via a Vayable Account 

As part of the Service, Vayable Users may communicate with Vayable Members through the Service. Where Vayable Users have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template may be sent from Vayable to those email addresses on their behalf. If so, such email addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending the email communication to the addressee. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Overview 

The Service can be used to facilitate the listing and booking of Experiences. Listings for such Experiences are made available via the Service by Guides. Listings posted by Guides, ratings and reviews of Members, and the Profile Information (as defined below) of Members, are visible to any Vayable User. 

Vayable Affiliates 

To enable or support us in providing the Service, we may share your information, including Personal Data, within our corporate family of companies (both financial and non-financial entities) that are related by common ownership or control. 

Vayable Members and Users 

When you create a Vayable Account, we will set up a Vayable Account profile page for you. Your Vayable Account profile page will include your first name and last initial. You can select the other items of Personal Data that you wish to be included in your Vayable Account profile page – including, but not limited to, a profile picture. We will display your Profile Information in your Vayable Account profile page publicly via the Service, and, with your prior permission, on third party sites. Any information you choose to provide as part of your Profile Information will be publicly visible to all Vayable Users and consequently should reflect how much you want other Vayable Users to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage members to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your Profile Information at any time. 

Listings 

If you post a Listing, we may publish that Listing publicly via the Service and may enable third parties to publish your Listing on their websites through the use of an HTML “widget”. We may also display the geographical location of your Listing in the form of a map so that potential Travelers can see the general area and neighborhood of your Listing, but the actual street address will not be disclosed until you enter into a confirmed transaction with another Member. If you request to make a booking via the Service, Vayable may share the following information about you with the applicable Guide: your first and last name and a link to your Vayable Account profile page. All of this information will enable the Guide to decide whether to confirm or reject your booking. When a Guide confirms a booking we may share pieces of the Guide’s Identify Information, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number, the Experience’s starting address and the Guide’s email address, with the applicable Traveler selected by the Guide and we may share pieces of the Traveler’s Identify Information with the Guide, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number and email address, so that the Traveler and Guide may contact one another directly. In no event is a Traveler's Billing Information shared with a Guide. 

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information 

We may share aggregated information that does not identify you personally and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not identify you personally. 

Service Providers 

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site and Application-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, fraud detection services relating to the activity of Vayable Users and improvement of the Service's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Data; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications. Third party vendors, like Google, may use cookies to serve ads based on a Vayable User's prior visits to Vayable. You can disable these specific cookies that track prior visits for the sake of follow-up advertising by opting out at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. 

Social Media Platforms. Where permissible according to applicable law we may use certain limited personal information about you, such as your email address, to hash it and to share it with social media platforms, such as Facebook or Google, to generate leads, drive traffic to our websites or otherwise promote our Service. These processing activities are based on our legitimate interest in undertaking marketing activities to offer you products or services that may be if your interest. social media platforms with which we may share your personal data are not controlled or supervised by Vayable. Therefore, any questions regarding how your social media platform service provider processes your personal data should be directed to such provider. Please note that you may, at any time ask Vayable to cease processing your data for these direct marketing purposes by sending an e-mail to opt-out@Vayable.com. with Laws and Law Enforcement; Guarantee Program Vayable cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Vayable or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials and to our insurance services providers as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to protect the property and rights of Vayable or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

Business Transfers 

If Vayable undertakes or is involved in any merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or insolvency event, then we may sell, transfer or share some or all of our assets, including your information in connection with such transaction or in contemplation of such transaction (e.g., due diligence). In this event, we will notify you before your personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Changing or Deleting Your Information 

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Data in their registration profile by contacting us at support@vayable.com or editing the relevant part of their profile. If you would like us to cancel your Vayable Account, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation or a legitimate business reason to retain the information contained in your Vayable Account. Please note that, if you cancel your Vayable Account, any reviews you have posted via the Service will remain publicly viewable via the Service. Please see below for privacy contact information. 

Security 

Vayable takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Service from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Service may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Vayable via the Internet. 

Analyzing your Communications. 

We may review, scan, or analyze your communications on the Service for fraud prevention, risk assessment, regulatory compliance, investigation, product development, research, and customer support purposes. For example, as part of our fraud prevention efforts, we scan and analyze messages to mask contact information and references to other websites. In some cases, we may also scan, review, or analyze messages to debug, improve, and expand product offerings. We use automated methods where reasonably possible. However, occasionally we may need to manually review some communications, such as for fraud investigations and customer support, or to assess and improve the functionality of these automated tools. We will not review, scan, or analyze your communications to send third party marketing messages to you, and we will not sell reviews or analyses of these communications. 

These activities are carried out based on Vayable's legitimate interest in ensuring compliance with applicable laws and our Terms, preventing fraud, promoting safety, and improving and ensuring the adequate performance of our services. 

Links to Other Websites 

Our Site and Application may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Data from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Data you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

Testimonials 

With your consent we may post your testimonial on the Service along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us. 

YOUR RIGHTS 

You may exercise any of the rights described in this section by sending an email to support@vayable.com. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before taking further action on your request. 

Managing Your Information. 

You may access and update some of your information through your Account settings. If you have chosen to connect your Vayable Account to a third-party application, like Facebook or Google, you can change your settings and remove permission for the app by changing your Account settings. You are responsible for keeping your personal information up-to-date. 

Rectification of Inaccurate or Incomplete Information. 

You have the right to ask us to correct inaccurate or incomplete personal information concerning you (and which you cannot update yourself within your Vayable account). 

Data Access and Portability. 

In some jurisdictions, applicable law may entitle you to request copies of your personal information held by us. You may also be entitled to request copies of personal information that you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and/or request us to transmit this information to another service provider (where technically feasible). 

Data Retention and Erasure. We generally retain your Personal Data for as long as is necessary for the performance of the contract between you and us and to comply with our legal obligations. If you no longer want us to use your information to provide the Service to you, you can request that we erase your Personal Data and close your Vayable account. Please note that if you request the erasure of your Personal Data: 

  * We may retain some of your personal information as necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as fraud detection and prevention and enhancing safety. For example, if we suspend an Vayable Account for fraud or safety reasons, we may retain certain information from that Vayable Account to prevent that Member from opening a new Vayable Account in the future. 
  * We may retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations. For example, we may keep some of your information for tax, legal reporting and auditing obligations. 
  * Information you have shared with others (e.g., Reviews, forum postings) may continue to be publicly visible on the Service, even after your Vayable account is cancelled. However, attribution of such information to you will be removed. Additionally, some copies of your information (e.g., log records) may remain in our database, but are disassociated from personal identifiers. 
  * Because we maintain the Service to protect from accidental or malicious loss and destruction, residual copies of your Personal Data may not be removed from our backup systems for a limited period of time. 

Withdrawing Consent and Restriction of Processing. 

Where you have provided your consent to the processing of your Personal Data by Vayable you may withdraw your consent at any time by changing your Account settings or by sending a communication to Vayable specifying which consent you are withdrawing. Please note that the withdrawal of your consent does not affect the lawfulness of any processing activities based on such consent before its withdrawal. Additionally, in some jurisdictions, applicable law may give you the right to limit the ways in which we use your personal information, in particular where: (a) you contest the accuracy of your Personal Data; (b) the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your Personal Data; (c) we no longer need your Personal Data for the purposes of the processing, but you require the information for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; or (d) you have objected to the processing as described here and pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of Vayable override your own. 

Objection to Processing. 

In some jurisdictions, applicable law may entitle you to require Vayable not to process your Personal Data for certain specific purposes (including profiling) where such processing is based on legitimate interest. If you object to such processing Vayable will no longer process your Personal Data for these purposes unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for such processing or such processing is required for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. 

Where your Personal Data is processed for direct marketing purposes, you may, at any time ask Vayable to cease processing your data for these direct marketing purposes by sending an e-mail to support@Vayable.com. 

Lodging Complaints 

You have the right to lodge complaints about the data processing activities carried out by Vayable before the competent data protection authorities. 

Our Policy Toward Children 

The Service is not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Data without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Data, we will delete such information from our files. 

Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@vayable.com. 

Last Updated: May 23, 2018 

Vayable, Inc. (“Vayable”, “we” or “us”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Data we receive from users of www.vayable.com (the “Site”) and any related applications (the “Application”) and otherwise, through the Service. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your Vayable Account) or by means of a notice via the Service prior to the change becoming effective. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service (at www.vayable.com). 

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally. 

International Transfer 

YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO - AND MAINTAINED ON - COMPUTERS LOCATED OUTSIDE OF YOUR STATE, PROVINCE, COUNTRY OR OTHER GOVERNMENTAL JURISDICTION WHERE THE PRIVACY LAWS MAY NOT BE AS PROTECTIVE AS THOSE IN YOUR JURISDICTION. IF YOU ARE LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES AND CHOOSE TO PROVIDE INFORMATION TO US, VAYABLE TRANSFERS PERSONAL DATA TO THE UNITED STATES AND PROCESSES IT THERE. YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOLLOWED BY YOUR SUBMISSION OF SUCH INFORMATION REPRESENTS YOUR AGREEMENT TO THAT TRANSFER. 

Information Collection and Use 

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, Application, services, features and content (collectively, the “Service”), to administer your use of the Service and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Service. 

Personally Identifiable Information 

When you register with us through the Service and become a Member and when you choose to post a Listing or book an Experience, or when you wish to contact another Member, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Identity Information”). Identity Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, email address, social security number (SSN), government-issued identification card, and home postal address, but does not include your credit card number or billing information. In order to process some of your transactions through the Service, we may also ask for your credit card number and other billing information (“Billing Information”). We may collect information about your precise or approximate location as determined through data such as your IP address or mobile device’s GPS to offer you an improved user experience. Most mobile devices allow you to control or disable the use of location services for applications in the device’s settings menu. Vayable may also collect this information even when you are not using the app if this connection is enabled through your settings or device permissions. (Identity Information, Billing Information and geolocation information together, “Personal Data”). If the address associated with a Listing you post matches that of your credit card billing address, that address would be considered Identity Information. Some Personal Data may be required, like your name and email address, and other Personal Data may be optional, like your date of birth. We use your Personal Data to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. 

We collect Personal Data in connection with your registration to join the Service. You can register to join via the Service by completing the required forms. 

You may also be permitted to register by logging into online accounts you may have with third party service providers (“SNS”) (e.g. Facebook); each such account, a “Third Party Account”, via the Service as described below. As part of the functionality of the Service, you may link your Vayable Account with Third Party Accounts, by either: (i) providing your Third Party Account login information to Vayable through the Service; or (ii) allowing Vayable to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to Vayable and/or grant Vayable access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for use for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating Vayable to pay any fees or making Vayable subject to any usage limitations imposed by the applicable SNS. If you decide to register by logging into a Third Party Account via the Service, we will obtain the Personal Data you have provided to the applicable SNS (such as your name, email address, profile picture, names of SNS friends, names of SNS groups to which you belong, other information you make publicly available via the applicable SNS and/or other information you authorize Vayable to access by authorizing the SNS to provide such information) from your Third Party Accounts and use that information to create your Vayable Account and Vayable Account profile page and you will become a Member. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, you understand that by granting us access to the Third Party Accounts, we will access, make available and store (if applicable and as permitted by the SNS and authorized by you) the information in your Third Party Accounts so that it is available on and through your Vayable Account on the Service. If there is information about your “friends” your Third Party Account, the information we obtain about those friends, may also depend on the privacy settings such people have with the applicable SNS. 

We may also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your Vayable Account profile (e.g., without limitation, zip code (on its own) and individual preferences or demographic information) (“Non-Identifying Information”). 

We use your Personal Data (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries. 

Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Data if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your demographic information). We may combine your Personal Data with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Vayable Users (defined below) to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how the Service is used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions. 

We also use your Personal Data to contact you with Vayable newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or contact us as detailed in the “Changing or Deleting Information” section, below. Please note that we may also use your Personal Data to contact you with information related to your use of the Service; you may not opt out of these notifications. 

Log Data 

When you visit the Service, whether as a Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “Vayable User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Service, pages of the Service that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on the Service, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Service and for the Service’s technical administration, to increase the Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor the Service to our visitors' and users’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to and users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Data or use it in association with other Personal Data, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information. 

Cookies 

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Service and help us analyze Service usage more accurately. For instance, our Service may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Service without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Service. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. Third party advertisers on the Service may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. We may also use Flash cookies, which operate differently than browser cookies and cookie management tools available in a web browser may not remove flash cookies. To learn more about and manage flash cookies you can visit adobe.com and make changes at the privacy settings panel. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Service or all functionality of the Service. 

Web Beacons 

Our Site and Application may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs), which would be used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how the Service is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This would allow us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns. 

Sending Messages Via a Vayable Account 

As part of the Service, Vayable Users may communicate with Vayable Members through the Service. Where Vayable Users have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template may be sent from Vayable to those email addresses on their behalf. If so, such email addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending the email communication to the addressee. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Overview 

The Service can be used to facilitate the listing and booking of Experiences. Listings for such Experiences are made available via the Service by Guides. Listings posted by Guides, ratings and reviews of Members, and the Profile Information (as defined below) of Members, are visible to any Vayable User. 

Vayable Affiliates 

To enable or support us in providing the Service, we may share your information, including Personal Data, within our corporate family of companies (both financial and non-financial entities) that are related by common ownership or control. 

Vayable Members and Users 

When you create a Vayable Account, we will set up a Vayable Account profile page for you. Your Vayable Account profile page will include your first name and last initial. You can select the other items of Personal Data that you wish to be included in your Vayable Account profile page – including, but not limited to, a profile picture. We will display your Profile Information in your Vayable Account profile page publicly via the Service, and, with your prior permission, on third party sites. Any information you choose to provide as part of your Profile Information will be publicly visible to all Vayable Users and consequently should reflect how much you want other Vayable Users to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage members to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your Profile Information at any time. 

Listings 

If you post a Listing, we may publish that Listing publicly via the Service and may enable third parties to publish your Listing on their websites through the use of an HTML “widget”. We may also display the geographical location of your Listing in the form of a map so that potential Travelers can see the general area and neighborhood of your Listing, but the actual street address will not be disclosed until you enter into a confirmed transaction with another Member. If you request to make a booking via the Service, Vayable may share the following information about you with the applicable Guide: your first and last name and a link to your Vayable Account profile page. All of this information will enable the Guide to decide whether to confirm or reject your booking. When a Guide confirms a booking we may share pieces of the Guide’s Identify Information, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number, the Experience’s starting address and the Guide’s email address, with the applicable Traveler selected by the Guide and we may share pieces of the Traveler’s Identify Information with the Guide, including, but not limited to, full name, phone number and email address, so that the Traveler and Guide may contact one another directly. In no event is a Traveler's Billing Information shared with a Guide. 

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information 

We may share aggregated information that does not identify you personally and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not identify you personally. 

Service Providers 

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site and Application-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, fraud detection services relating to the activity of Vayable Users and improvement of the Service's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Data; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications. Third party vendors, like Google, may use cookies to serve ads based on a Vayable User's prior visits to Vayable. You can disable these specific cookies that track prior visits for the sake of follow-up advertising by opting out at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. 

Social Media Platforms. Where permissible according to applicable law we may use certain limited personal information about you, such as your email address, to hash it and to share it with social media platforms, such as Facebook or Google, to generate leads, drive traffic to our websites or otherwise promote our Service. These processing activities are based on our legitimate interest in undertaking marketing activities to offer you products or services that may be if your interest. social media platforms with which we may share your personal data are not controlled or supervised by Vayable. Therefore, any questions regarding how your social media platform service provider processes your personal data should be directed to such provider. Please note that you may, at any time ask Vayable to cease processing your data for these direct marketing purposes by sending an e-mail to opt-out@Vayable.com. with Laws and Law Enforcement; Guarantee Program Vayable cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Vayable or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials and to our insurance services providers as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to protect the property and rights of Vayable or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

Business Transfers 

If Vayable undertakes or is involved in any merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or insolvency event, then we may sell, transfer or share some or all of our assets, including your information in connection with such transaction or in contemplation of such transaction (e.g., due diligence). In this event, we will notify you before your personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Changing or Deleting Your Information 

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Data in their registration profile by contacting us at support@vayable.com or editing the relevant part of their profile. If you would like us to cancel your Vayable Account, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation or a legitimate business reason to retain the information contained in your Vayable Account. Please note that, if you cancel your Vayable Account, any reviews you have posted via the Service will remain publicly viewable via the Service. Please see below for privacy contact information. 

Security 

Vayable takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Service from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Service may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Vayable via the Internet. 

Analyzing your Communications. 

We may review, scan, or analyze your communications on the Service for fraud prevention, risk assessment, regulatory compliance, investigation, product development, research, and customer support purposes. For example, as part of our fraud prevention efforts, we scan and analyze messages to mask contact information and references to other websites. In some cases, we may also scan, review, or analyze messages to debug, improve, and expand product offerings. We use automated methods where reasonably possible. However, occasionally we may need to manually review some communications, such as for fraud investigations and customer support, or to assess and improve the functionality of these automated tools. We will not review, scan, or analyze your communications to send third party marketing messages to you, and we will not sell reviews or analyses of these communications. 

These activities are carried out based on Vayable's legitimate interest in ensuring compliance with applicable laws and our Terms, preventing fraud, promoting safety, and improving and ensuring the adequate performance of our services. 

Links to Other Websites 

Our Site and Application may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Data from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Data you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

Testimonials 

With your consent we may post your testimonial on the Service along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us. 

YOUR RIGHTS 

You may exercise any of the rights described in this section by sending an email to support@vayable.com. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before taking further action on your request. 

Managing Your Information. 

You may access and update some of your information through your Account settings. If you have chosen to connect your Vayable Account to a third-party application, like Facebook or Google, you can change your settings and remove permission for the app by changing your Account settings. You are responsible for keeping your personal information up-to-date. 

Rectification of Inaccurate or Incomplete Information. 

You have the right to ask us to correct inaccurate or incomplete personal information concerning you (and which you cannot update yourself within your Vayable account). 

Data Access and Portability. 

In some jurisdictions, applicable law may entitle you to request copies of your personal information held by us. You may also be entitled to request copies of personal information that you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and/or request us to transmit this information to another service provider (where technically feasible). 

Data Retention and Erasure. We generally retain your Personal Data for as long as is necessary for the performance of the contract between you and us and to comply with our legal obligations. If you no longer want us to use your information to provide the Service to you, you can request that we erase your Personal Data and close your Vayable account. Please note that if you request the erasure of your Personal Data: 

  * We may retain some of your personal information as necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as fraud detection and prevention and enhancing safety. For example, if we suspend an Vayable Account for fraud or safety reasons, we may retain certain information from that Vayable Account to prevent that Member from opening a new Vayable Account in the future. 
  * We may retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations. For example, we may keep some of your information for tax, legal reporting and auditing obligations. 
  * Information you have shared with others (e.g., Reviews, forum postings) may continue to be publicly visible on the Service, even after your Vayable account is cancelled. However, attribution of such information to you will be removed. Additionally, some copies of your information (e.g., log records) may remain in our database, but are disassociated from personal identifiers. 
  * Because we maintain the Service to protect from accidental or malicious loss and destruction, residual copies of your Personal Data may not be removed from our backup systems for a limited period of time. 

Withdrawing Consent and Restriction of Processing. 

Where you have provided your consent to the processing of your Personal Data by Vayable you may withdraw your consent at any time by changing your Account settings or by sending a communication to Vayable specifying which consent you are withdrawing. Please note that the withdrawal of your consent does not affect the lawfulness of any processing activities based on such consent before its withdrawal. Additionally, in some jurisdictions, applicable law may give you the right to limit the ways in which we use your personal information, in particular where: (a) you contest the accuracy of your Personal Data; (b) the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your Personal Data; (c) we no longer need your Personal Data for the purposes of the processing, but you require the information for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; or (d) you have objected to the processing as described here and pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of Vayable override your own. 

Objection to Processing. 

In some jurisdictions, applicable law may entitle you to require Vayable not to process your Personal Data for certain specific purposes (including profiling) where such processing is based on legitimate interest. If you object to such processing Vayable will no longer process your Personal Data for these purposes unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for such processing or such processing is required for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. 

Where your Personal Data is processed for direct marketing purposes, you may, at any time ask Vayable to cease processing your data for these direct marketing purposes by sending an e-mail to support@Vayable.com. 

Lodging Complaints 

You have the right to lodge complaints about the data processing activities carried out by Vayable before the competent data protection authorities. 

Our Policy Toward Children 

The Service is not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Data without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Data, we will delete such information from our files. 

Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@vayable.com. 

Last Updated: August 19, 2013 

These terms and conditions govern the Vayable Traveler Refund Policy (the “Traveler Refund Policy”) available to Travelers who book and pay services related to travel Providers through the Vayable platform (the “Site”) and suffer a Travel Issue and the obligations of the Guide associated with the Traveler Refund Policy. Some Providers (“Guides”) lead experiences on the ground, and other Providers (“Insiders”) help with travel planning. 

##### Refunds and cancellation for your trip planned by Vayable Insiders

Travelers are free to reject any Itinerary for any reason prior to payment. Once an Itinerary is confirmed by a Traveler, any fees paid are non-refundable except as set forth below: 

**Traveler cancels** Vayable will endeavor to refund Traveler the fees paid for any Itinerary items that have not yet been booked, minus the Service Fee. Fees for Itinerary items that have already been booked are non-refundable. 

**Provider cancels** Whenever possible Vayable will connect Traveler to an alternate Provider who can fulfill request. If not, Vayable will refund the Total Fees for such booking to the applicable Traveler within a commercially reasonable time of the cancellation. 

**Cancellation due to outside factors** Certain Experiences may depend on factors outside either party’s control, such as weather (“Outside Factors”). The Provider has the discretion as to whether Outside Factors will prevent the Experience from taking place. As a Provider, if you need to cancel an Experience due to Outside Factors, you must contact the Traveler and Vayable (at [support@vayable.com](mailto:support@vayable.com)) as early as possible. Subject to the Traveler’s consent, the Provider and the Traveler may choose to reschedule the Experience for another date. If the Experience cannot be rescheduled, the Traveler should contact Vayable so we may assist in finding a replacement Experience. For clarity, in the event the alternative Experience is of a higher price than the former, you may be responsible for any difference in price. In the event the alternative Experience is of a lower price, you may be entitled to a partial refund for the difference. As a Traveler, if you have contacted Vayable as provided above and Vayable is unable to find you a replacement Experience, Vayable may refund the Total Fees for such booking to the applicable Traveler within a commercially reasonable time of the cancellation. 

##### Refunds and cancellation for your experience led by Vayable Insiders

**1.Travel Issue.** A “Travel Issue” means any one of the following: 

a) The Guide of the Experience (i) cancels a reservation within 24 hours before the scheduled start of the reservation, (ii) fails to arrive for the Experience within 20 minutes of the scheduled start time, or (iii) fails to provide the Traveler with the reasonable ability to access the Experience (e.g., by allowing the Traveler access to the space in which the Experience will happen or begin if applicable). 

b) The description of the Experience in the listing on the Site is materially inaccurate with respect to (i) the duration of the Experience, (ii) the content of the Experience (including but not limited to the stated activities or sites, as applicable), or (iii) the physical location of the Experience. c) During the Traveler’s Experience, conditions do not meet safety or health hazards that would be reasonably expected, given the nature of the particular Experience, in Vayable’s judgment. 

**2\. The Traveler Refund Policy.** If you are a Traveler and suffer a Travel Issue, we agree, at our discretion, to either (i) reimburse you up to the amount paid by you through the Site, as determined by Vayable in our discretion, depending on the nature of the Travel Issue suffered or (ii) use our reasonable efforts to find and book you another Experience which in our determination is reasonably comparable to the Experience described in your original reservation in terms of content and quality. For clarity, in the event the alternative Experience is of a higher price than the former, you may be responsible for any difference in price. In the event the alternative Experience is of a lower price, you may be entitled to a partial refund for the difference. All determinations of Vayable with respect to the Traveler Refund Policy, including without limitation the size of any refund, shall be final and binding on the Travelers and Guides. 

**3\. Conditions to Claim a Travel Issue.** Only a Traveler may submit a claim for a Travel Issue. If you are a Traveler, in order to submit a valid claim for a Travel Issue and receive the benefits with respect to your reservation, you are required to meet each of the following conditions: 

a) You must report the Travel Issue to Vayable in writing (at support@vayable.com) or via telephone and provide us with information (including evidence) about the Experience and the circumstances of the Travel Issue within 24 hours after the start of your reservation, and must respond to any requests by us for additional information or cooperation on the Travel Issue; 

b) You must not have directly or indirectly caused the Travel Issue (through your action, omission or negligence); and 

c) You must have used reasonable efforts to try to remedy the circumstances of the Travel Issue with the Guide prior to making a claim for a Travel Issue (and you must provide evidence of having done so). 

**4\. Minimum Quality Standards, Guide Responsibilities and Reimbursement to Traveler.** If you are a Guide, you are responsible for ensuring that the Experiences you list on the Site meet minimum quality standards regarding adequacy of the description on the Site, safety, health, and do not present a Traveler with Travel Issues. Throughout the Experience, Guides should be available in order to try, in good faith, to resolve Traveler issues. 

If you are a Guide, and if (i) Vayable determines that a Traveler has suffered a Travel Issue related to an Experience listed by you and (ii) Vayable either reimburses that Traveler any amount up to the amount paid by the Traveler through the Site for the Experience or provides an alternative Experience to the Traveler, you agree to reimburse Vayable up to the amount paid by Vayable within 30 days of Vayable’s request. All determinations of Vayable with respect to the Traveler Refund Policy, including without limitation the size of any refund to the Traveler, shall be final and binding on the Travelers and Guides. You also agree that in order for you to reimburse Vayable up to the amount paid by Vayable, Vayable may off-set or reduce any amounts owed by Vayable to you by this amount. If the Traveler is rescheduled to an alternative Experience, you may lose part or all of the Experience Fee payment for the booking and you may be responsible for reasonable additional costs incurred to reschedule the Traveler to the alternative Experience. 

The rights of the Travelers under the Traveler Refund Policy supersede the cancellation policy that otherwise applies to a particular Experience. If you dispute the Travel Issue you may notify us in writing (support@vayable.com) or via telephone and provide us with information (including evidence) disputing the claims regarding the Travel Issue, provided you must have used reasonable and good faith efforts to try to remedy the Travel Issue with the Traveler prior to disputing the Travel Issue claim (and you must provide evidence of having done so). You agree that all determinations of Vayable with respect to the Travel Issue shall be final and binding on the Travelers and Guides regardless of your submission of a dispute against such Travel Issue. In the event of one or more 

Travel Issues, Vayable, in its discretion, may elect to take additional actions. These actions include, but are not limited to, negatively affecting your listing ranking, automated reviews or notifications indicating Travel Issues, canceling future bookings, suspending or removing the listing of the Experience or imposing penalties or fees for the administrative burden associated with the Travel Issues. 

**5\. General Provisions.**

a) No Assignment/No Insurance. This Traveler Refund Policy is not intended to constitute an offer to insure, does not constitute insurance or an insurance contract, does not take the place of insurance obtained or obtainable by the Traveler, and the Traveler has not paid any premium in respect of the Traveler Refund Policy. The benefits provided under this Traveler Refund Policy are not assignable or transferable by you. 

b) Modification or Termination. Vayable reserves the right to modify or terminate this Traveler Refund Policy, at any time, in its sole discretion, and without prior notice. 

c) If Vayable modifies this Traveler Refund Policy, we will post the modification on the Site or provide you with notice of the modification and Vayable will continue to process all claims for Travel Issues made prior to the effective date of the modification. 

d) Entire Agreement and Definitions. This Traveler Refund Policy constitutes the entire and exclusive understanding and agreement between Vayable and you regarding the Traveler Refund Policy and supersedes and replaces any and all prior oral or written understandings or agreements between Vayable and you regarding the Traveler Refund Policy. Capitalized terms not otherwise defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in the Vayable Terms of Service. Controlling Law. This Traveler Refund Policy will be interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of California and the United States of America, without regard to its conflict-of-law provisions. 

e) Limitation of Liability. IN NO EVENT WILL VAYABLE’S AGGREGATE LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS VAYABLE POLICY TERMS, EXCEED THE AMOUNT OF THE EXPERIENCE FEES COLLECTED BY VAYABLE FROM THE TRAVELER. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT, BY POSTING A LISTING OR BOOKING AN EXPERIENCE OR OTHERWISE USING THE SITE, SERVICES AS A GUIDE OR TRAVELER, YOU ARE INDICATING THAT YOU HAVE READ, AND THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE POLICY TERMS. **6\. Contacting Vayable.** If you have any questions about the Traveler Refund Policy, please contact Vayable at support@vayable.com. 

Last Updated: August 06, 2014 

##### Referring a Friend

Any user registered with Vayable can refer a friend. You do not need to have ever booked an experience or be an Insider. The person using your referral code is your referral. Referral codes may only be used for non-commercial purposes, meaning you may only share your invite link with personal connections via email, Twitter, Facebook, and your own blogs. You agree you will not publish or distribute the link, or cause the link to be published or distributed, on or via methods, platforms and media where you do not have reasonable basis for believing that all or most of the readers or recipients are your personal connections (including coupon websites, forums, and public wikis). 

##### Getting and Applying Credits

Vayable will apply credit to your Vayable account within 48 hours after your referral's qualifying reservation takes place. After your referral successfully completes a qualifying reservation, you will be credited with the determined U.S. dollar amount (or its equivalent in your local currency if we support it). We will automatically apply the total amount of the credits you earn to your next qualifying reservation in the form of a coupon, which you will see on the booking check-out page. You may not combine credits with any additional coupon, gift card or promotion. Credits expire after three years from the date that they are issued. 

##### Qualifying Reservation

A qualifying reservation means a booking with a total value of $75 or more. All reservations must be booked on the Vayable website or mobile application, and successfully completed by the referral for you to qualify to receive credits. A reservation that is subsequently canceled, refunded or altered such that the total value becomes less than $75 disqualifies it for credits. In order for a reservation to qualify, you also cannot be the Traveler or Insider on the reservation, and the traveler and insiders cannot both be referred by you. 

##### Referrals with Multiple Links/Codes

Your will only receive credit after a qualifying reservation when a referral uses your referral link or code to sign up for an account on Vayable. If your referral signs up using a different referral code or link to sign up, you will not receive the travel credit. 

##### Limited Time Only

This incentive program is for a limited time only. Vayable at any time may end or suspend this incentive program (entirely or just a part of it). We may also change the requirements and incentives at any time. 

##### Receiving a Referral Invite to Join Vayable

You will receive a credit for the stated promotion amount. Sign up by clicking on a valid referral link or using a valid referral code from an existing Vayable user and you’ll receive a credit for the promotional amount to use toward your next qualifying reservation on Vayable. 

Alternatively, you can enter a referral code in the Apply Credit link when making your first reservation. You can view your credit in the Travel Bank section your user profile page. 

Vayable reserves the right to suspend any account sand remove referrals for any activity we deem to be abuse of the referral program. 

Notification of Copyright Infringement: 

Vayable, Inc. (“Vayable”) respects the intellectual property rights of others and expects its users to do the same. Unless otherwise defined in this Copyright Policy, terms used in this Copyright Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service (at www.vayable.com/terms). 

It is Vayable’s policy, in appropriate circumstances and at its discretion, to disable and/or terminate the account or access of users who repeatedly infringe or are repeatedly charged with infringing the copyrights or other intellectual property rights of others. 

In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, the text of which may be found on the U.S. Copyright Office website at <http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf> Vayable will respond expeditiously to claims of copyright infringement that are reported to Vayable’s Designated Copyright Agent, identified in the sample notice below. 

If you are a copyright owner, or are authorized to act on behalf of one, or authorized to act under any exclusive right under copyright, please report alleged copyright infringements taking place on or through the Services by completing the following DMCA Notice of Alleged Infringement and delivering it to Vayable’s Designated Copyright Agent. Upon receipt of the Notice as described below, Vayable will take whatever action, in its sole discretion, it deems appropriate, including removal of the challenged material from the Services. A notification of claimed copyright infringement should be emailed to Vayable’s Copyright Agent at [terms@vayable.com](mailto:terms@vayable.com) (Subject line: “DMCA Takedown Request”). You may also contact us by mail at: 33 Rausch St., San Francisco, CA 94103. 

#### DMCA Notice of Alleged Infringement (“Notice”)

To be effective, the notification must be in writing and contain the following information: 

  * an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other intellectual property interest; 
  * a description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed; 
  * a description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Service, with enough detail that we may find it on the Service; 
  * your address, telephone number, and email address; 
  * a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright or intellectual property owner, its agent, or the law; 
  * a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you are the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act on the copyright or intellectual property owner’s behalf. 

#### Counter-Notice

If you believe that your content that was removed (or to which access was disabled) is not infringing, or that you have the authorization from the copyright owner, the copyright owner’s agent, or pursuant to the law, to upload and use such content, you may send a written counter-notice containing the following information to Vayable’s Designated Copyright Agent (“Counter-Notice”): 

  * your physical or electronic signature; 
  * identification of the content that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the content appeared before it was removed or disabled; 
  * a statement that you have a good faith belief that the content was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or a misidentification of the content; and 
  * your name, address, telephone number, and email address, a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of the federal court located within Northern District of California and a statement that you will accept service of process from the person who provided notification of the alleged infringement. 

Upon receipt of the Counter-Notice by Vayable’s Designated Copyright Agent, Vayable will send a copy of the Counter-Notice to the original complaining party informing that person that it may replace the removed content or cease disabling it in 10 business days. Unless the copyright owner files an action seeking a court order against the content provider, member or user, the removed content may be replaced, or access to it restored, in 10 to 14 business days or more after receipt of the counter-notice, at Vayable’s sole discretion.
